Somebody did somebody wrong song.
How to say you're sorry.
This is Doctor Paul, author of Boomer Girls: A Boomer Woman's Guide to Men and Dating and host of Ask Doctor Paul.
How to say I'm sorry, number one, don't overdo it, all right.
If you say sorry every time you turn around whenever you say sorry is never going to be believed.
So when you say you're sorry, be believable.
If you use the term all the time it loses its impact.
So, number one, how to say you're sorry, do it with believability.
I have often had callers say, well I told him I'm sorry and I say okay, is that how you said it?
How did you say you're sorry?
Oh, right, did you have a couple of drinks and sit there and cry and slobber and say I'm sorry?
Well that's not going to get it, is it?
When you say you're sorry you must do it quietly, don't scream it, I've heard that before.
You sit quietly and look, I'm deeply sorry, use an adjective before it.
I'm really sorry, I'm deeply sorry, I'm objectively sorry.
I feel horribly sorry.
Use something more than just sorry, I'm sorry, no, means nothing.
If you're going to do it, mean it, don't do it very often.
It loses its impact.
If you have to do it very often it means you're obviously doing something wrong, and that goes for man or woman.
Okay.
I'm sorry is not good enough.
Even writing it down can be helpful.
Getting a card that says I'm really, truly sorry for what occurred, whatever the incident may be.
And there are greeting cards out there with that.
So if you're going to say you're sorry, the only thing Doctor Paul suggests is be believable.
This is Doctor Paul, may your fantasies of today be your realities of tomorrow.